{
    "subject": "Noboru_Iguchi",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "The_Machine_Girl",
    "human_readable": "Noboru Iguchi directed the film The Machine Girl.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8598856925964355,
            "question": "Who directed the film The Machine Girl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8365452289581299,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Noboru Iguchi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8310774564743042,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Noboru Iguchi."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7440751791000366,
            "question": "Is Noboru Iguchi a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5524676442146301,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Noboru Iguchi that you know of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.410398006439209,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of The Machine Girl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37561747431755066,
            "question": "What is the year The Machine Girl was released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3172934353351593,
            "question": "Has Noboru Iguchi won any awards for his films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31724366545677185,
            "question": "What genre is The Machine Girl likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2930797040462494,
            "question": "Where can I watch The Machine Girl?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Noboru Iguchi directed the film The Machine Girl.",
            "html": "yago_17983_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is The Machine Girl likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_17983_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Noboru Iguchi won any awards for his films?",
            "html": "yago_17983_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the year The Machine Girl was released?",
            "html": "yago_17983_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17983_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17983_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17983_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17983_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17983_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17983_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17983_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17983_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17983_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17983_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason is that all the documents mention that Noboru Iguchi wrote and directed the film \"The Machine Girl\", which confirms this triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Noboru Iguchi is the director of the film \"The Machine Girl,\" which directly supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}